

# Nayeli A. Pérez T.

nayeliperez.com

nayeliaperezt@gmail.com (915) 449 • 3373

San Antonio, TX

nayelip 🗓

nayeliprz11

Hello! My name is Nayeli Pérez; nice to meet you. I am a multidisciplinary designer with a keen interest in user interface design, front-end development, and the overall challenge of designing digital experiences in an increasingly digital world. I also particularly enjoy the challenges of branding/identity design and design systems.

### **EDUCATION**

AUG 2012 - MAY 2016 Bachelors of Arts in Communication, CUM LAUDE

Minor in Studio Art & Art History - Photography Concentration

Trinity University - San Antonio, TX

FALL 2015 Study Abroad

Studio Art Centers International (SACI) - Florence, Italy

### RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

AUG 2013 - DEC 2015 Photographer

Trinity University Campus Publications - San Antonio, TX

Photographed for The Trinitionian (university newspaper) and The Mirage (Yearbook)

JAN 2015 - MAY 2016 Graphic Design Intern

Trinity University Press - San Antonio, TX

Responsible for creating digital and print-ready branding material and marketing collateral, including website banners and posters, large print banners, galley covers, and print ads

JAN 2016 - MAY 2016 Art Director

Trinity University's Skyline 2016 Magazine - San Antonio, TX

- → Skyline is a publication written, designed, and produced by students at Trinity University's Communication department. As art director I was tasked with coming up with the overall visual style of the magazine; the main goal of the magazine was to provide an exhibition space for the best of Trinity University's student magazine writing
- → I worked closely with the managing editor along with our faculty advisors to put together a style guide and subsequently layouts that would position Skyline as a professional, streamlined student publication

# LANGUAGES

Spanish & English
Native Speaker

# SKILLS

InDesign

Photoshop

Illustrator

Lightroom

AfterEffects

Sketch

Figma

Invision

Wordpress

HTML/CSS

**Bootstrap** 

Javascript

Extensive Photography and Darkroom Printing Experience

#### AUG 2016 - PRESENT Head of Design

#### esd & Associates Digital Marketing - San Antonio, TX

- → Develop creative for traditional media (i.e. billboard, poster, flyer, etc.) for both long-term marketing campaigns and short-term projects that require a quick turnaround
- → Work closely with developer team to design website and app interfaces for projects ranging from landing pages to mobile apps (i.e. fleshing out wireframes, using Sketch, Figma, Illustrator to create screen mockups & assets, creating prototypes with InVision)
- → Implement sites using Wordpress
- → Implement landing pages using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap
- → Use of Mailchimp and Salesforce to create engaging e-blasts and promotional communication
- → Creating logomarks, brand identities, and brand guidelines
- → Project-manage large designed pieces such as RFPs, large manuals for healthcare clients, etc. (i.e.design, compile copy and data from all departments, build infographics, strategize and discuss creative, manage deadlines)

## **REFERENCES**

#### **Kristen Villareal**

Account Manager
esd and Associates Digital Marketing - San Antonio, TX
kristenrv@gmail.com
(210) 685 • 5639

### Joseph Garcia

Business Marketing Strategist esd and Associates Digital Marketing – San Antonio, TX josephagarcia12@gmail.com (210) 325 • 7542

#### **Cole Evans**

Founder and President
Confadent Oral Technology - Denver, CO
cole@confadent.com
(720) 495 • 2402
I have consistently done design & production work (packaging, sales sheets, etc.) for Cole for the past three years.